<?xml version="1.0"?>
<document>
  <name>Simon Standbridge</name>
  <address>Saucestown&#xD;
Fethard&#xD;
Co Tipperary&#xD;
&lt;p&gt;Test clean_input&lt;/p&gt;</address>
  <picture>&lt;img src='C:\wamp64\www\SSP2\A1\Simon_Standbridge\uploads\150894514012545259_907553499358837_2049013391_n.jpg'/&gt;</picture>
  <dob>1993-06-05</dob>
  <exp>Forecourt Assistant&#xD;
Company NameAmber Petrolium&#xD;
Dates EmployedNov 2014 &#x2013; Present  Employment Duration3 yrs 1 mo&#xD;
Customer service, i.e helping customers with and of their fueling or any general assistance around the forecourt of the petrol station. 6 years Experience in this field.&#xD;
Edit position IT Intern Ireland Chauffeur Travel&#xD;
IT Intern&#xD;
Company NameIreland Chauffeur Travel&#xD;
Dates EmployedJun 2017 &#x2013; Aug 2017  Employment Duration3 mos&#xD;
LocationCashel Co. Tipperary&#xD;
At Ireland Chauffeur Travel my responsibilities include regular upkeep and maintenance of the Ireland Chauffeur Travel website, assisting in digital marketing campaigns and assisting the office staff with any IT related queries they may have. During my time at Ireland Chauffeur Travel my HTML, CSS and PHP skills were enhanced as well as my design skills, and I became very familiar with the WordPress environment.&#xD;
Edit position Shop Assistant Bourkes Daybreak&#xD;
Shop Assistant&#xD;
Company NameBourkes Daybreak&#xD;
Dates EmployedNov 2011 &#x2013; Nov 2014  Employment Duration3 yrs 1 mo&#xD;
Edit position Crew Member McDonald's Corporation&#xD;
Crew Member&#xD;
Company NameMcDonald's Corporation&#xD;
Dates EmployedMay 2011 &#x2013; Sep 2011  Employment Duration5 mos</exp>
  <edu>Limerick Institute of Technology&#xD;
Degree NameBachelor of Science - BS (hons) Field Of StudyCreative Multimedia&#xD;
Dates attended or expected graduation 2017 &#x2013; 2018&#xD;
Final year add on for the Creative Multimedia Programme at Limerick Institute of Technology Clonmel. Undertaking final year project to investigate the organization and display of records and results for a sporting federation via a webapp.&#xD;
Edit education Limerick Institute of Technology Reorder education {:name} Limerick Institute of Technology&#xD;
Limerick Institute of Technology&#xD;
Degree NameBachelor's degree Field Of StudyCreative Multimedia GradeDistinction&#xD;
Dates attended or expected graduation 2014 &#x2013; 2017&#xD;
Partook in web development and multimedia in college, and familiarized myself with the Adobe Creative Suite. Keen on learning the art of programming and honing my skills to make a name for myself in the Multimedia world. Received distinction grades in every programming based module to date in Limerick Institute of Technology, with an distinction grade overall in the Creative Multimedia program.&#xD;
Edit education University of Limerick Reorder education {:name} University of Limerick&#xD;
University of Limerick&#xD;
Degree NameBachelor's Degree Field Of StudyComputer Games Design and Development&#xD;
Dates attended or expected graduation 2012 &#x2013; 2014&#xD;
My introduction into computer programming via Java. This enhanced my future ventures into Web Programming where I honed my programming skills.</edu>
</document>
