<?xml version="1.0"?>
<document>
  <name>Simon Standbridge</name>
  <address>Saucestown,&#xD;
Fethard,&#xD;
Co. Tipperary,&#xD;
e91 v440</address>
  <picture>&lt;img src='C:\wamp64\www\SSP2\A1\Simon_Standbridge\downloads\150892227812545259_907553499358837_2049013391_n.jpg'/&gt;</picture>
  <dob>1993-06-05</dob>
  <exp>November 2014-Present: Shop and forecourt assistant at Amber Petroleum, Clonmel:&#xD;
&#xD;
Duties included serving customers both inside the shop, and dispensing fuel to customers on the forecourt. Trusted with handling large sums of money on a weekly basis, as well as trusted with the shop keys and password to alarm.&#xD;
&#xD;
October 2011-November 2014:   Shop Assistant at Bourkes Daybreak, Killenaule: &#xD;
			&#xD;
Duties included working the tills for both store items and for petrol, I worked mostly alone in the shop so I had a lot of responsibility as regards running the shop and general upkeep of the shop. I built a relationship with the locals of the town as it is a rural area and many regulars came into the shop daily who began to know me by name. I was trusted to cash up alone at the end of each night, and also to lock and secure the shop. I was trusted with a key to the shop along with the password to the alarm.&#xD;
&#xD;
June 2011-September 2011:  Crew member at McDonalds, Cashel:&#xD;
&#xD;
Duties included preparing food to order. Taking payment and giving change. Keeping work area clean and cleaning of ovens, fridges and freezers and taking stock every Sunday.&#xD;
	&#xD;
</exp>
  <edu>September 2014-Present: LIT Clonmel Campus&#xD;
&#xD;
Currently undertaking a B.Sc. in Creative Multimedia in LIT Clonmel campus, expected graduation June 2018. Emphasis on programming, web development along with graphic design and audio/video. Achieved Second-class Honours in both first and second years of study with distinctions in every programming-based module to date.&#xD;
&#xD;
Technical Skills:&#xD;
&#xD;
Proficient in: &#xD;
JavaScript				ActionScript&#xD;
HTML					Java	&#xD;
CSS					Adobe Creative Suite&#xD;
C#					Microsoft Office Suite&#xD;
Microsoft Office suite			3d Modelling (Maya)&#xD;
Node.JS				Version Control (GitHub)	&#xD;
				&#xD;
Notable Projects:&#xD;
&#xD;
Responsive website for local exhibition &#x201C;Pen and Pixel&#x201D; (2016)&#xD;
As part of a solo project, I was assigned the task of creating a responsive website for a local exhibition which contained a gallery and some other information about the exhibition.  &#xD;
&#xD;
&#x201C;Mick the Mouse&#x201D; (2016)&#xD;
As part of a group of 2, myself and a fellow student developed a short, 2d platform game for our interactive programming class. This was achieved in the Flash environment using ActionScript 3.0, it was also ported to android devices.&#xD;
&#xD;
&#x201C;Clouds&#x201D; (2017)&#xD;
	As part of a team of 2, myself and a fellow student designed and developed a mini game which was published to the Google Play Store. This project was a 14 week long assignment which was a substantial portion of my Batchelor degree. Clouds was developed using ActionScript 3.0 and is available at: &#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
&#xD;
September 2006-June 2012: Scoil Ruain Secondary School, Killenaule&#xD;
&#xD;
Achieved 405 points of a maximum of 600 in my leaving cert, including 5 honours subjects. I also achieved both bronze and silver level in the Gaisce awards in 2010 and 2011 respectively.&#xD;
</edu>
</document>
